Starting a Gradle Daemon, 1 incompatible and 2 stopped Daemons could not be reused, use --status for details

[Incubating] Problems report is available at: file:///C:/Users/art69/IdeaProjects/paymentsystem/paymentService/build/reports/problems/problems-report.html

Deprecated Gradle features were used in this build, making it incompatible with Gradle 9.0.

You can use '--warning-mode all' to show the individual deprecation warnings and determine if they come from your own scripts or plugins.

For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/8.14/userguide/command_line_interface.html#sec:command_line_warnings in the Gradle documentation.
